golfwrx.com 2012-11-11

# GolfWRX.com – Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

We gather certain types of information about the visitors to the GolfWRX Network , and we believe our visitors should fully understand how we obtain and use that information. This Privacy Statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, you should contact us at management@golfwrx.com.

**Your Personal Information**

The submission by you to us of personally identifiable information (e.g., your e-mail address) is required in order for you to receive services, products or information you request from either us or companies with which we do business. (We refer to such personally identifiable information, as well as any other information that you voluntarily provide to us about yourself on the GolfWRX Network that we combine with your personally identifiable information, as your “Personal Information.”) Your Personal Information will be shared between us and those companies, and may also be disclosed to other entities who work with us or those companies to fulfill your request.

While we will not use your Personal Information to send you commercial emails unless you have given us your consent, we may use both your Personal Information and other information we may have about you (such as your IP address) or your use of the GolfWRX Network (such as which pages you have visited) to customize or enhance your experience on the GolfWRX Network, including the display of advertisements. In addition, and as described in greater detail in our Membership Agreement, if you are a member of the GolfWRX Network we may send you certain administrative and service messages in connection with our Community Services; you cannot opt out of receiving those communications.

**Access to Your Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you would like to delete any of your personally identifiable information, you may correct, update or delete it by either (i) modifying your Membership account, or (ii) sending a request to us through our Contact Us form.

**Other Cookies**

“Cookies” are small data files that many Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file contains information such as a user ID that a site may use to track the pages you’ve visited. However, the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. Cookies served by us don’t permit us to read data from your hard drive or to read cookie files created by other Web sites.

We use cookies in many ways, including the following:

First Visits: When you first visited the GolfWRX Network, we served a cookie to you. This cookie resides permanently on your hard drive (unless you chose to delete it) and enables us to track visitor activity across our Web sites.

Membership Registration: When you register as a member of the GolfWRX Network, we use a cookie to store your registration information on your computer if you click the “Remember me” box. We use this cookie to enable you to enter the GolfWRX Network as a member without having to sign in each time.

Advertisements: Our advertising results in the serving of cookies that facilitate the delivery and administration of such advertising. See “Third-Party Ad Servers” below.

Advertisers: The current Advertising Terms and Conditions for advertisers on the GolfWRX Network provide that advertisers may write cookies to our visitors’ computers solely for advertising campaign tracking and management purposes, but not for advertisement “retargeting” (i.e., for the purpose of targeting advertisements to visitors to an GolfWRX Web site when they subsequently view other (non- GolfWRX) Web sites).

Please note that we do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our Web sites.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Website, please use our Contact Us form.

**Our Community Services**

The GolfWRX Network provide a number of means by which you may communicate with other visitors and with us. Many of these are the various communication and personalization tools and services that are part of our “community” (the “Community Services”). In order to add content to the GolfWRX Network through the Community Services, you must first become a member of the GolfWRX Network and agree to our Membership Agreement. (You do not need to register in order to browse or read the content provided by our members.) The Membership Agreement sets forth a number of information sharing and disclosure practices for our Community Services, and accordingly supplements this Privacy Statement.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or allow such persons to become members of the GolfWRX Network. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register as a member or send any information about yourself to us. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us through our Contact Us form.

**Surveys**

Occasionally we conduct visitor surveys to better target our content to our audience or for the benefit of third parties with whom we do business. Accordingly, sometimes the aggregate survey results are shared with our advertisers and partners. We never share any survey information about specific response with any third party unless that individual consents.

**E-mail this Page to a Friend**

Many of the pages of the GolfWRX Network include a feature that permits visitors to electronically forward that page to someone else by clicking on a link. The sender must provide his or her e-mail address, as well as that of the recipient. The sender’s information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the page. Neither the sender’s information nor the recipient’s information is used for any other purpose.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

The GolfWRX Network contains links to many other Web sites not operated by us, including sites where you can obtain products and services. However, this Privacy Policy only applies to the GolfWRX Network and the information we collect, and we are not responsible for the privacy polices or practices of any other Web sites.

**Third-Party Ad Servers**

We use DoubleClick Inc., a third-party advertising company, to serve advertisements for the GolfWRX Network. We also sometimes use other third-party advertising companies and advertising networks to serve ads. DoubleClick and these other third-party advertising companies and advertising networks may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to the GolfWRX Network and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We also may place “Web beacons” on pages of the GolfWRX Network which, in conjunction with cookies utilized by our third-party advertising companies, are used to target advertisements on the GolfWRX Network and other Web sites. Web beacons, sometimes called “pixel tags,” are small strings of code that are placed on Web pages. Use of our third party advertising companies’ cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies to target advertisements to you, you may [view DoubleClick’s privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/privacy-policy.html) or visit [www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion and at any time, to change this Privacy Statement. Changes will be effective when made and the updated Privacy Statement is posted on the GolfWRX Network; _provided, however,_ that (i) information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the provisions of this Privacy Statement that applied at the time the information was collected, and (ii) no such change shall be applicable to any dispute between you and us that arises prior to the time such change is effective. Accordingly, you should visit this page periodically to review its provisions. Your continued use of the GolfWRX Network following the posting of changes to this Privacy Statement will mean you accept those changes.
